Hey hello guys welcome back to my channel what are
we going to talk about now good
morning first of all what happened to you like there was
a
minor accident with the vehicle, I had hit a minor one on it
not a bike, this one which is a
tour, this one of ours was set at 62
and there are some minor injuries on this too, I had fun
okay so already some of our
friends and it was on the road so
he wanted to make an insurance claim to them,
how to do insurance claim, this
famous Sara and we are going to tell you
in this video so see we go straight to the point
what happened like the law enforcers
we cleaned the
turn off on 14th February and from that time
inspector Safdi Alembert was on duty,
he came to inspect us,
after that what happened, there was a injury on our bumper also, the
left leg was broken, the bumper was
already slightly broken, by the way that was there and on the right
also apart from that they did not
give it to us brother so what had to be done, we had to get it done from
him, that's for you  First tell me
what else is there for you, these two pollution filled
first doors should be there, it was completely pressed,
this has been changed, this channel has come down, the
fruit of the outside, this
point has been changed, let me show you,
before that, let me show you that you
could see here, there was a little bit of it stuck here, it has
not come out that well on the album, but the price is
not known yet,
after that it was fixed here, it was
completely done here, it has
completely covered all this, there is no problem with the number 1 color,
but there is a problem, we
will tell you that it was pressed from here, you
also do it properly, so this is our new one, it is
different and its number 11, here it has
not changed from the house, it was there
but it has not changed, this
door of ours has got dented back, where
something was stuck here, very much, then from here there is a
big major said major of death somewhere here,
all this has been fixed completely properly
and after that, this police station which we got on low flame, what did you do with it,
this
front front and this lado  It was in replacement
and this cutting was passed
and then I show you this at the end, like
here in the photo of the fire, it was completely rusted here,
friend brother, it was already there a little earlier, so
what did we have to do to get it repaired, I
mean, first they were saying that
it has to be repaired, so
why not repair it, so after talking to them and
requesting them, they
attacked from their side, the service center people did it,
okay, then it
is very important to maintain a relationship with the service center people, so
this is our repair, I mean it was not free,
they did it from their side,
what happened after that, all this was done with him and mom,
so mom does not like the work at all, all this had happened
here,
somehow it was repaired here,
they did not do this also, this which you installed for a while
on the left side, you can see
how it was repaired because there is
another side, so the people here were
not giving the capacity, so what happened to it, we had to get it repaired
and the bike was repaired very cheaply
because we had talked to them, the
company did the work, but this is the total
bill that we presented for it  Did it happen around 80, it happened on
865, on this bomb, on the
left side of this side, on the left and right side, they
chopped a little bit of Dhanota,
they painted it, it is completely complete,
okay, now
brother, what happened to you, first of all we have a clear
court on the night, both of them had hit it outside, I do
n't know where it had hit it, it had
come completely on the front screen, we went to the service
center again and fixed it by sandpaper, it had
completely become rough, it was making noise when we
moved our hands, like you see here,
how is the paint here, if we are applying it with our
hands, then it is there, if
you are applying it here, there is no such tool,
but look at this also, the Bullet is completely
ruined, it will have to be cancelled, I have
applied Darshan Mitti from outside only, I was
washing it like that, I want to see
how the sound is being made here, look once
and look at the paste here, it
is absolutely fine here and like sand here
[Music]
okay, okay, this is the thing done,
all that will have to be done, it can be felt by touching only, there is
no problem on the stomach, after that I did the next one
here  But I don't know who was the fool,
friend, now look here, someone has
left a fingerprint, if you look carefully at it, you will see
on the sensor
that yes, there is a mark on the wrapper of someone's fingerprint, the
creature said this there, so
they said that now this is a new print, if we
rub it then it might get removed
completely, so give it some time, after that we will
fix it, then we will update it further,
they will not have to fix this, then all
this is clearly defective from here, all this is
completely ruined, all this should be done
from outside, it is a
work of ₹500, that dishonest person who does not do it, it will be
completely fixed by hitting it,
here it is lying very lightly at some places,
after that now let's go inside the pack and the
problem was that they
forgot to make a video of this one which is returning us, so this goes here
and then as soon as the door panel got changed, who
knows, it might have happened to them, the whole world must have got damaged,
this lock had to be
changed due to lack of it, what happened was that as soon as we were
locking the car, we decided to
unlock it, that means  The door is open but
I was not sleeping there on the ID, this
warning is not on my back, this rule is
burning, okay, so we were unlocking it, is there
any indication, so what
happened with that, once we went to the garage,
so we unlocked this one and during the locker the
key was left inside and when we closed it, the
car got locked, we did
not even realize that it was unlocked, the car
is prevented from moving and it will happen again,
you can see this is a completely new lock, the
underwear has been changed,
by the way, we did not have to pay any money, this is
old, so how does it look and it is
not at all changed,
120 paper clips have been changed,
you can see after that, we go to Welingkar,
now if we talk about the bell,
leave this, leave this also, today Salman has been installed, he would have
told you that if
this was a normal love, then he did
not pay any of this to the company, what all happened to the insurance company,
then
he has prepared almost Rs 10,000 for all this regarding the door also  The
door was lying for 10200 for the first year
fee of 1028, after that there is metallic color
printing front door, all this is recharge of
₹4000 for Netflix India, all this is
normal, this is the total bill,
our hotel bill is 26 thousand nine four
means two 80, you have received its total in Bilha,
from this the company has passed it,
put bus and metro, the amount has been received from there,
claim number so much for the car
2106, that is okay and this is our front for
1000 rupees, okay,
so we did 2 -, so this is the model
2030 office, we had to pay it, okay, so
you people must also be thinking that the
payment is from thousand to 15 years, this is the
insurance claim from the company, but the car,
he told after sitting well and explained that
if the car is one year old, then what is the
depression amount on it, he
told something like this which is 10 percent of the purchase, so it is
deducted on that, so this is the model 2030 of the office  It was a door of 10,000, it is
not possible, the total together was
10,000, that is 10 per cent application
collected and on this we had to pay the remaining
1,000 extra, please subscribe our
file,
so do
not forget to subscribe because you should subscribe to this channel
and this is our ready,
Tasleem's process is correct, you just
go and get only one form, you have to
fill it,
you have to tell about the type of accident and you have to fill the date a little,
how it looks a little real, in
cases like if you already have a car, then you
can adjust a little in making it free,
how it has to be done, so this was
our video today, the total cost came out,
print the rate of repairing, comment section, it is a
big door change because it has happened, so that is all till today
brother,
thank you for watching the video, if you liked the video
then like the video and subscribe to this channel, we will meet
you like this
in the next video, bye
Jhal